newsvoir.com 2019-06-17

# Privacy Policy

**This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for NewsVoir.com, a brand owned and operated by ClickStream Media Pvt. Ltd.**

This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:

  * What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared
  * What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data
  * The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information
  * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information

#####  **Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**

We are the sole owners of the user information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, such as your media contact details included in the press releases.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

**Registration and Security**

We may collect and store the following personal information: email addresses, physical contact information, telephone numbers, computer sign-on data, statistics on page views, traffic, to and from the site, and ad data among other information, and this data may also include IP addresses and standard web log information.

All on-line data collection as defined above, and billing for our services, will be protected by Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology that encrypts your information during transmission, with details about NewsVoir obtainable within our Security Certificate, part of SSL technology.

No financial and transactional data such as credit card numbers, are kept by NewsVoir in any way, and our customer contact policies comply with all applicable laws, rules and regulations.

**Opting out**

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website.

**Cookies**

We use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.

**Links**

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

**Our Policy towards children**

This site is not directed to children. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personal information without their consent, he or she should contact us via our “Contact us” page.

**Updates**

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.

For any queries/clarifications, reach us at [info@newsvoir.com](mailto:info@newsvoir.com), or call us on the numbers given in the Contact us page
